Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
Oden                   Girls Swim Club
（梅原）よっとっと…
（薫）ホッと…
（詞）みんな～ッ　みんなのお陰で
創設祭の準備も
Everyone!
Thanks to you all, all that's left to do is decorate the Christmas tree.
あとクリスマスツリーの
飾りつけだけです
It looks like we'll successfully make it for the Founder's Festival.
何とか無事
創設祭を迎えられそう
本当に　ありがとう
Thank you all... so much.
Isn't it a little too early for that, Ayatsuji-san?
（ヤヨイ）それはまだ
早いんじゃないの？　絢辻さん
That's right.
そうだよ　ちゃんと本番を
迎えられてからにしてくれよ
Save that for after we've actually had the festival.
（笑う一同）
You're right.
そうね
Yes, you're right.
うん　そうだね
Tomorrow is the long-awaited Founder's Festival.
いよいよ明日は創設祭です
Let's work hard together until the very end!
最後まで　みんなで力を合わせて
頑張りましょう
Yeah!
（一同）お～ッ！
《（純一）あの子が
いなくなっちゃったって》
What do you mean, that girl no longer exists?
《どういうこと？》
So you mean you have a split personality,
and that side of you disappeared yesterday?
《絢辻さんが二重人格者で》
《昨日までの人格が
消えちゃったとか》
《そういうこと？》
《二重人格者か～》
So I have a split personality?
That's an interesting way to explain it.
《それは　おもしろい解釈だね》
《でも　ハズレ》
But that's wrong.
《じゃあ　どういうことなの？》
Then what is it?
《とにかく　昨日までのあの子は
いなくなっちゃったの》
In any case, that girl ceased to exist yesterday.
《それだけ覚えておいて》
That's all you need to remember.
《さあ　みんなが待ってるよ》
Well, everyone's waiting.
《早く戻って創設祭の準備しよう》
Let's go back and continue
preparing for the Founder's Festival!
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
どうしたの？　ボーッとしちゃって
Why are you daydreaming?
Uh, well... nothing at all.
ああ　いや　何でもないよ
Come on, Tachibana-kun, let's go decorate the Christmas tree with everyone else!
ほら　橘君もみんなと一緒に
クリスマスツリーの飾りつけやろう
ごめん
Sorry.
備品の最終チェックとか
I still need to do the final equipment check and some committee work.
実行委員の仕事が
まだ残ってるんだ
ちょっと行ってくる
I'll be back.
Best of luck!
頑張ってね
I do think Ayatsuji-san's cute right now.
〈今の絢辻さんは
かわいいと思うよ〉
〈悪くないと思う〉
Not bad at all.
The class atmosphere is also much livelier.
〈クラスの雰囲気も
明るくなったし〉
〈でも…〉
But...
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
・～
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
With our fears of possible bad weather gone,
we can commence the 57th
Founder's Festival here this evening!
Before we begin, I'd like to thank the members of my class, 2-A,
for helping with the Christmas Tree decorations and other preparations.
Thank you so much, everyone!
And now, with gratitude to all of you who assisted,
as well as all of our visitors...
I now announce the opening of the 57th annual Founder's Festival!
Did you watch me, Tachibana-kun?
見ててくれた？　橘君
あッ　うん　スピーチ立派だったよ
Y-Yeah.
Your speech was great.
ありがとう
Thank you.
キレイだね　クリスマスツリー
Isn't the Christmas tree pretty?
みんなのお陰
It's all thanks to everyone.
うん　そうだね
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Final Chapter
Promise
Yeah.  You're right.
・（ヤヨイ）絢辻さーん
Ayatsuji-san.
・（みゆき）早く～
Hurry up.
は～い　ちょっと待って
Ah, okay!
Just a minute!
空き時間に　ヤヨイちゃん達と
見て回る約束したの
I promised to walk around with Yayoi-chan and her friends during my free time.
Tachibana-kun, do you want to come with us?
橘君も一緒にどう？
Oh nah, I'm...
ああ　いや　僕は…　ごめん
Sorry...
そう　残念
Ah, that's a shame.
じゃあ　またあとでね
Well, I'll see you later.
（逢）いらっしゃいませ～
Welcome!
An egg and Chikuwa, right?
卵とちくわですね
少々　お待ちください
Just a moment, please.
（美也）ギャ～オ～ッ
かわいい子ウサギちゃんめ
Raawwwr!
You adorable little rabbit!
I'm having you for dinner!
食べちゃうぞ～ッ
Oh...?
（紗江）
あ～れ～　おやめくださいまし
Please stop, o great one!
お代官様～
さあ　続いて
エントリーナンバー７番
Moving right along, entry number seven!
ミス　サンタコンテスト２連覇中
She's won the Miss Santa Contest twice in a row.
The one you've all been waiting for...
皆さん　お待ちかねの
Morishima Haruka-senpai!
森島はるか先輩～ッ！
Whoa!
That outfit's risky!
Wow!
Very risky, Morishima-senpai!
I knew this would happen.
Hey, do you think I can get away with this outfit?
It was acceptable when I was the one wearing it...
Haruka suddenly decided she wanted to compete.
But...
Well, she seems to be having fun, so whatever.
Everyone!
（男子達）おお～ッ！
I'm counting on you, okay?
・（薫）お～っと～ッ！
Miss Santa Contest
ギリギリです
ギリギリですよ　森島先輩～ッ
It'll probably be Morishima-senpai again.
（響）やっぱり　こうなるわよね
She's really pretty, after all.
It looks like she'll score her third victory.
《（はるか）ねえ　この衣装
ホントにセーフなの？》
Hey, Ayatsuji-san, don't you also think Morishima-senpai's gonna win?
《私が着る分には
許容範囲だったんだけど…》
I don't know.
Everyone's really cute, so I can't really say for sure.
はあ～　はるかが
いきなり出たいっていうから
Sorry, Yayoi-chan.
でも　まあ楽しそうにしてるから
いっか
It's about time I returned to the committee work.
Okay, later then.
See you at the after party!
Sweets!  Sweets!
みんな～ッ！
Wait!
よ・ろ・し・く
You only get one sweet each.
ねッ！
Hey, don't touch me down there!
Ahh, don't put your hand in there!
（みゆき）やっぱり森島先輩かな～
Rihocchi sure is popular with the kids.
（ゆーこ）美人だもんね～
She's a good girl, after all.
Ｖ３　達成しちゃいそう
ねえ　絢辻さんも
やっぱり森島先輩だと思う？
Ooh, that sweet sake is looking good.
Takahashi-sensei!
どうかな～　みんな
かわいい人ばっかりだから
You can't have any.
私　分からないな
Come on, just because I got a little wild last year?
ごめんね　そろそろ
実行委員の仕事に戻らなくっちゃ
I'll be fine with just one cup.
じゃあ　またあとで
打ち上げでね～
I don't trust you.
I sense disaster approaching.
・（梨穂子）純一
Junichi!
よう　梨穂子
（梨穂子）来てくれたんだ
Yo, Rihoko.
So you came.
見回りのついで　約束してたからな
Yeah, during my rounds.
I promised, after all.
繁盛してるみたいじゃないか
Looks like things are going well.
お陰さまでね
Thank you very much.
純一も飲んでいってよ
Junichi, you should have something to drink.
Tea?  Or maybe some sweet sake?
お茶？　それとも甘酒にする？
Ah no, nothing for me.
いや　僕はいいよ　すぐ帰るし
I have to go soon anyway.
Junichi, is something bothering you?
純一　なんか元気ない？
No, it's nothing like that.
そんなことないよ
（琉璃子）りほっち
子供達がお菓子待ってるぞ～
Rihocchi.
These kids are waiting for their snacks.
Oh, sorry!
すみませ～ん　すぐ行きま～す
I'll be right there!
じゃあ　ごめんね　純一
I'm sorry, Junichi.
ううん　頑張れよ　梨穂子
It's cool.
Hang in there, Rihoko.
うん
Yep!
Here you go.
お待たせ
（香苗）ヤッホー　桜井
遊びにきたよ
Hey, Sakurai!
I came to see you!
香苗ちゃん
おッ　モテモテじゃん
Kanae-chan!
Ooh, aren't you popular?!
エヘヘヘヘヘ
Why did Ayatsuji-san become like that?
〈絢辻さん　どうして　あんなふうに
なっちゃったんだろう〉
〈悪くはないんだ　でも…〉
It's not exactly a bad thing, but...
〈だったら　どうして僕は
こんなにモヤモヤしてるんだ？〉
Why am I feeling so gloomy about it?
うん？
梅原
Umehara...
Wait!
待て！
あッ？
うわ～ッ！
考え直せよ！
Think it over!
Just because you couldn't find a girlfriend this year...
今年も
彼女ができなかったからって
It doesn't mean you have to start a fire in your despair!
放火だなんて　やけにならなくても
あッ…
I see.
そっか　小学校のときにもらった
ラブレターだったのか
So it was a love letter from your elementary school days.
Yeah, that's what it is.
まあ　そういうことだ
でも　何で　今さら？
But why now?
I mean, back then...
あの頃ってよ
誰かを好きとか嫌いとか
Wasn't it really uncool to love or hate someone?
そういうのが
カッコわりいとか思ってただろ？
Yeah, it was.
ああ　そうだな
So I stubbornly refused to write her a reply.
だから俺　意地張って
返事　書かなかったんだけど
それを今んなって
もったいねえとか後悔してんだ→
It's such a shame now that I think back on it.  I really regret it!
だからよ　いつまでも未練がましく
持ってるんじゃなくて→
So instead of holding on to my regrets forever,
いっそ　すっぱり
燃やしちまおうと思ってな
I figured I'd just burn it and be done with it.
You have my respect.
潔いな
よくねえよ
Don't respect me!
今になって後悔しまくりだ
All I do now is regret!
Regret, huh?
後悔…　か
どうした？　大将
What is it, boss?
僕　またダメだったよ
I failed again.
今年のクリスマスは頑張るとか
言ってたくせに情けないよ
Even though I said I'd try my best for Christmas this year.
It's pathetic.
何言ってんだよ
えッ？
What are you talking about?!
Christmas Eve isn't over yet!
クリスマスイブは
まだ終わってねえだろ
情けねえって思ってんなら
行動するしかねえんじゃねえのか
If you feel like you're pathetic, then do something about it!
Before you regret it like me.
俺みたいに後悔する前によ
ありがとう　梅原
Thanks, Umehara...
お前　いいやつだな
だろ？
You really are a good guy.
何で彼女できないんだろうな
I know, right?
I wonder why you can't get a girlfriend...
それを言うな　泣けてくるぜ
Shut up.
You'll make me cry.
メリークリスマス
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス
Merry Christmas!
うわ～ッ　やった！
Whoa, heck yes!
絢辻さんから　もらっちゃった
I got a present from Ayatsuji-san!
はい　メリークリスマス
Here, Merry Christmas.
中身は　お菓子よ
There's candy inside.
いらない
Don't want it.
Kibitou High School
Founder's  Festival
以上をもちまして
第５７回　創設祭は終了いたします
And with that, the 57th Founder's Festival comes to an end.
Thank you all very much for attending.
ご来場　まことに
ありがとうございました
Please have a wonderful night.
素敵な夜をお過ごしください
・（男子Ａ）それでは　第５７回
創設祭の無事終了を祝って→
Now then, in celebration to a
successful 57th Founder's Festival...
乾杯！
Cheers!
（一同）乾杯！
本当にありがとう
Thank you all so much.
It's all thanks to everyone.
全部みんなのお陰だよ
That's not true at all.
そんなことないよ
絢辻さんが頑張ったからだよ
It's because you worked so hard, Ayatsuji-san.
忙しかったけど結構楽しかったよ
There was lots to do, but it was pretty fun.
Yep, yep!
うんうん
They say that preparing for the festival is
when you have the most fun, and it's true.
祭りは準備してるときが　一番
楽しいっていうけど　ホントだな
The more hectic it is, the sadder you'll feel once it's all over.
大変だった分
終わっちゃうのが少し寂しいぜ
Kaoru, you were great as the contest MC.
（恵子）薫　コンテストの司会
決まってたよ
Really?
そう？　本当はサンタコスでコンテストに
出てもよかったんだけどね→
I actually wanted to participate in the Santa costume contest.
Well, Morishima-senpai scored her third victory in a row this year...
まッ　今年は見事　森島先輩が
Ｖ３を達成したわけだし→
So it was a good thing I skipped work to be the MC.
バイト入れずに
司会やった甲斐があったわ
あッ　橘君
Tachibana-kun.
何やってたの？
もう打ち上げ始まっちゃってるよ
Where were you?
The after party started without you.
うん　ごめん
Ah, sorry.
You should've come to see me too.
橘君も
見にきてくれればよかったのに
I was really popular as Santa Claus!
私のサンタさん
みんなに大人気だったんだから
あのさ　絢辻さん
You know, Ayatsuji-san...
Hmm?  What?
うん　なあに？
ちょっと　いいかな？
Do you have a minute?
話って　何？
You wanted to talk?
うん
Yeah.
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
I still have people to give my thanks to, so I'm going back to the classroom.
私　まだみんなにお礼を
言い終わってないから
教室に戻るね
好きだ
I love you.
・（男子Ａ）おせーぞ　梅原
何やってたんだよ
You're late, Umehara.  Where were you?
My bad, but the hero's supposed to show up last.
わりいな　でも
主役は最後に登場するもんだろ
And who said you're the hero?
・（薫）誰が主役よ　誰が→
You were barely around for the Founder's Festival too.
創設祭　ほとんどいなかったくせに
・（梅原）ちょっと　ヤボ用でな
I had some business to attend to.
・（恵子）どうせまた
フラれたんでしょ
I bet you got rejected again anyway.
（笑う一同）
Thank you, Tachibana-kun.
ありがとう　橘君
I'm happy.
嬉しいよ
私も橘君のことが…
Me too, I like-
I...
僕は…
I have an unpleasant Christmas memory,
so I don't handle this time of the year well.
僕はクリスマスに
嫌な思い出があって
この時期が苦手だった
It was so bad that I ran away from
attending the Founder's Festival last year.
去年の創設祭も参加できずに
逃げ出したくらいなんだ
でも　ずっと
このままじゃいられないと思って
But I knew that I couldn't stay like this forever, so I volunteered to be on the committee.
実行委員に立候補した
I figured I'd work hard this Christmas...
今年のクリスマス
頑張ろうと思って
And I ended up doing work with you, Ayatsuji-san.
それで絢辻さんと一緒に
仕事するようになって
覚えてるかな？
Do you remember?
僕が絢辻さんの
手帳を拾ったときのこと
When I picked up your notebook.
あのあと　神社に連れて行かれて
You brought me to the shrine after that.
絢辻さんにあんな一面が
あったなんて本当に驚いたよ
I was really shocked that you had that side to you.
でも　知ってよかった
But...
I'm glad I found out.
絢辻さんに
あれこれ叱られながら仕事して
You told me off for various things while I did my work.
It was tough since there was lots to do, but it was fulfilling to say the least...
忙しくて大変だったけど
充実してたというか
うん　クリスマスへの
苦手意識を感じてる時間もなくて
Yes, I didn't even have the time to think about how much I dislike Christmas...
いつの間にか
消えちゃったくらい楽しかった
It was so fun that the thought had disappeared before I knew it.
I think that was when I fell in love with you, Ayatsuji-san.
多分　その頃から僕は
絢辻さんのことが
好きになっていったんだと思う
橘君
うん？
Tachibana-kun.
Do you hate the way I am now?
今の私は　嫌い？
I don't.
嫌いじゃないよ
I like the way you are now too.
今の絢辻さんも好きだよ
But...
でも…
でも？
But?
僕は　前の意地っ張りな絢辻さんも
The obstinate Ayatsuji-san from before...
And the Ayatsuji-san who puts on an act of friendliness...
その前の
猫をかぶってた絢辻さんも
I like them all.
全部ひっくるめて好きなんだ
That's why I don't want you to tell me sad things like part of you has disappeared.
だから　いなくなったなんて
寂しいこと　言わないでほしい
I'd like you to scold me if there's anything I need to improve.
また僕の至らないところが
あったら叱ってほしい
それを伝えたくて
That's what I wanted to tell you.
何で？
えッ？
Why?
Why are you saying this?
何でそんなこと言うの？
絢辻さん？
Ayatsuji-san?
イテッ！　うわッ！
Ow-
何なのよ！　何なのよ　あんたは！
What was that?!
What the heck do you want?!
I tried to erase the real me because of what you said...
あんたがあんなこと言うから
だから私は
自分を消えたことにして
なのに…
But...
よかった
Thank goodness.
The Ayatsuji-san I love still exists.
僕の好きな絢辻さんが
ちゃんといた
（号泣する詞）
（麻耶）なあに～？
What?
What... was that noise?
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
何なの？　今の音は？
（田中）高橋先生
えッ？
Takahashi-sensei.
さっき　こちらから
すごい音がしましたが…
I heard a loud scream coming from this direction...
It's nothing!
何でもないんです
Sorry!
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
すみません
私が甘酒にちょっと酔って転んで
I got a little drunk from the sweet sake and fell over,
so I screamed, "Ouch!" without thinking...
思わず　あいた～ッ！　なんて…
お騒がせしました
Sorry about the noise.
さあ　田中先生
私達も打ち上げに行きましょう
Well, Tanaka-sensei, we should go to the after party too.
Founder's Festival Planning
Committee Headquarters
Ah... uh, okay.
えッ　あッ　はあ…
〈まったく…　仕方ないわね〉
Geez, you guys are hopeless.
This will be my Christmas present to you.
〈これは私からの
クリスマスプレゼントよ→〉
あ～ッ　私も彼氏が欲しい！
Ahh, I want a boyfriend too!
（田中）ええ？　まず高橋先生は
もう少しお酒を控えないと
Uh...
I think you should start by cutting back on your alcohol...
CONGRATULATIONS!!
FOUNDER'S FESTIVAL SUCCESS!
THERE'S A KARAOKE
AFTER-PARTY!!
Ouch...
イテッ
少しくらい我慢しなさい
Take this little bit of pain at least.
This was your fault in the first place.
もともとは
あなたが悪いんじゃない
Huh?
ええ～？
女の子に後ろから抱きつくなんて
It's sexual harassment to hug a girl from behind.  Sexual harassment.
セクハラよ　セクハラ
I'm sorry.
すみません
聞いてもらってもいい？
何？
Mind if I tell you something?
What?
It's about my past.
昔の話なんだけどね
うん
Okay.
One day, I realized that Santa Claus doesn't exist.
ある日　私はサンタさんが
いないことを知ったの
And the reality of it hit me hard...
それも現実を突きつけられて
えッ？
Huh?
よくある話だと　両親がプレゼントを
入れてる姿を見た　とか
I know this happens a lot, but I basically saw my parents place the presents under the tree.
そんな感じ
It was worse in my case though.
私の場合は
もっとひどかったけどね
I-In what way?
どんなふうに？
それは秘密
That's a secret.
I see.
そっか
And so, I made a decision having realized that Santa doesn't exist.
でね　サンタがいないと知った私は
そのときに決めたのよ
That I would become Santa.
私がサンタになるんだって
本物になれないことは分かってた
I knew that I couldn't become the real thing.
でも　サンタみたいなことなら
できるって考えたの
But I thought that I could become something like Santa.
サンタみたいなこと？
そう
Something like Santa?
Yes.
クリスマスイブ　みんなに
幸せをプレゼントすること
I could bring happiness to everyone by giving them presents.
And that's why you volunteered for the planning committee?
もしかして
それで創設祭の実行委員に？
うん
Yeah.
自分の力で　みんなが少しでも
クリスマスを幸せに過ごせるなら
If I could make everyone's Christmas even just a little happier through my own efforts...
それって素敵なことじゃない？
うん　そうだね
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
Yeah, you're right.
子供の頃　輝日東高校の
創設祭へ遊びにきて
I attended the Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival when I was a kid.
私　思ったの
This was what I thought.
この創設祭を
自分の手で成功させれば
If I could make the Founder's Festival a success with my own hands...
Wouldn't I bring happiness to everyone?
みんなを
幸せにできるんじゃないかって
But that was no good.
でも　ダメね
みんなを幸せにするって目的が
いつの間にか
Before I knew it, my aim of bringing happiness to everyone changed into one of satisfying myself.
私の満足感を満たすためのものに
変わってた
That's not true!
そんなことないよ
みんな楽しそうにしてたし
Everyone had fun.
ありがとう　でも　子供には
分かっちゃうものなのね
Thanks.
But it was something even a kid could tell.
My Santa Claus was well received among my peers...
私のサンタクロース
大人には評判よかったけど
子供は　なついてくれなかった
...but the kids didn't warm up to it at all.
さすがに絢辻さんも
子供は　だませなかったようだね
It looks like even the great Ayatsuji-san is unable to deceive children.
うん？
ああ…
橘君の言うとおりね
I suppose you're right.
まだクリスマスは終わってないよ
えッ？
Ayatsuji-san.
Christmas isn't over yet.
Huh?
来年も再来年も
クリスマスはまた来る
Christmas will come again next year and the year after.
そのたびに　みんなを
幸せにすればいいじゃないか
Why don't you just bring happiness to everyone each time?
そうね
You're right.
だから…
うん？
That's why...
だから…
僕のことも幸せにしてほしい
I'd also like you to bring me happiness.
それは
女性から言うセリフでしょ？
Isn't that what the girl is supposed to say?
ダメかな？
You don't want to?
ダメじゃないけど…
I don't mind, but...
（風が吹く）
Ahh, your hair's all messed up now.
ああ　髪がクシャクシャだ
大丈夫よ　自分でやるから
It's fine, I'll straighten it myself.
But...
でも…
I love you too, Tachibana-kun.
私も　橘君のこと好きよ
I won't ever let you go.
もう絶対に離さない
それって契約？
ううん
Is that an agreement?
No.
It's a promise.
約束
I love you from my heart
・～
I love you forever with you
Mujaki na sono egao wa
無邪気なその笑顔は
That innocent smile
Watashi dake ga shitteru
私だけが知ってる
I'm the only one who knows about it
Igai to amaenbou na anata no koto
意外と甘えん坊なあなたのこと
And just how unexpectedly spoiled you really are
Tsukahara Hibiki
Kodomo mitai ni sunao ne
子供みたいに素直ね
You're as honest as a child
Otoko wa sukoshi kuuru na
男は少しクールな
"Guys are supposed to be cooler!"
Kurai ga kakkoii to ijimetari
くらいがカッコいいとイジメたり
That's what I say to tease you
Donna toki mo kono te wo hanasanaide
どんな時もこの手を離さないで
Don't ever let go of my hand
Saigo no koi ni shiyou tte chikatta koto
最後の恋にしようって誓ったこと
We promised that we'd be in love forever
Ima wa mada naisho ni shite okou ka
今はまだ内緒にしておこうか
Maybe I'll keep it as my own secret for now
いいのかな？
You sure it's okay?
Hitori de niyaketeru gozen reiji sugi
一人でニヤけてる　午前０時過ぎ
As I lay there past midnight grinning to myself
いいわよ　これくらい
Yes, it's fine.
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
わあ～ッ
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
—10 Years Later—
ママ～ッ　パパ～ッ
Mama!  Papa!
Hey hey, is it this?
ねえねえ　これでしょ？→
Papa and Mama's memory tree.
パパとママの
思い出のツリーって
That's right.
そうだよ　ここでパパとママは
大事な約束をしたんだ
This was where Papa and Mama made an important promise.
約束？　どんな？
Promise?
What kind?
Hey, Junichi.
ねえ　純一
何？　詞
What is it, Tsukasa?
今　幸せ？
Are you happy now?
もちろんだよ
Of course I am.
私も幸せよ
I'm happy too.
あーッ　私も　チュッ
Oh, me too!
世界中の人達が
今日　このよき日に
I wish that everyone in the world can be happy on this wonderful day...
幸せでありますように
Just like us, right?
僕達みたいにね
Yes.
ええ
Merry Christmas!
・～
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
歩道を飾る　青いイルミネーション
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the swarming crowd
にぎわう人込みにひとりたたずむ
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
こぼれそうな笑顔
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
寄り添う恋人達
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
今の私には全てが
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
まぶしくて見れないの
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
誰かに愛されるでしょうか
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding underneath a facade
強がりの奥に隠れた
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please realize that
「わたし」に気付いてよ
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
本当に自由になれるでしょうか
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
どうか教えて
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
冬の町に迷い込んだ
Samishige na tenshi ga nageku
The lonely angel sighs
さみしげな　天使が嘆く
Yasashiku
Gently
優しく
Preview
Next episode preview.
Nii-nii, there's something I want to ask.
What?
What would you do if a cute girl you
didn't know confessed to you one day?
Huh?  What's that?
Whatever, just answer me!
So what would you do?
Hmm... I'd be happy if the girl who confessed is cute...
But I can't just say okay if I don't know her very well.
Oh?  I wasn't expecting such a respectable answer from you.
Next episode: "Truth".
Next Episode
Kamizaki Risa Arc
Truth
That winter memory where I was rejected surfaces once again...